Hi, I'm Keith Fitzpatrick, this is hip hop aerobic moves and we're going to go over our jumping jack change.
So with this one, this is kind of like regular jumping jack, but I put a ball change in there to kind of switch it up when we're doing the warm up.
So all we're doing is we're starting our regular position here.
We're jumping here, we jump here, we jump back here then we change and a change there.
So we go up and up and a change, a change and up here, up here, and change, and change.
So all you do is make sure you start here in center.
You want to jump all the way here, all the way up, all the way here, all the way back, then change, then change, and you're here, here, here, here, and change out and change out.
Make sure you get the bend in your knees.
Don't cheat.
Make sure you come here, and back.
Bump here, bump here, and change, and change.
There's your jumping jacks change.